http://www.mcccu.com/privacy-and-security

LOGIN
Your Privacy and Security are Important to UsWe are committed to protecting your privacy and safeguarding your personal and financial information. While the Internet is revolutionizing the way that we do business by providing convenient access to financial services from your home or office, we also recognize that it may bring legitimate concerns about privacy and security.Please refer to our Privacy Code and Online Privacy below to learn more about our commitment to your privacy and this website.
BROWSE SECURITY INFORMATION
Browser Requirements
Enhanced Security
Identifying Fraud
Protect Yourself Online
Legal
Report Lost/Stolen Card
Privacy Code
At Motor City Community Credit Union we are deeply committed to protecting our membership's personal privacy. In order to protect all personal information collected, used or disclosed by Motor City Community Credit Union, we have adopted the Credit Union Code for the Protection of Personal Information.It is our policy to protect all personal information by implementing and enforcing the following ten privacy protection principles derived from the Code as specified under the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPED Act). The following ten interrelated privacy principles are specified in the PIPED Act, and form the basis of the Code:Accountability: We are responsible for personal information under our control and have designated the Chief Financial Officer as the Privacy Officer who is accountable for our compliance with the principles of the Code.Identifying Purposes: We will identify the purposes for which personal information is collected before we collect the information.The credit union shall collect personal information for the following purposes:To confirm identity of the memberTo understand the member’s needs;To determine the suitability of the products or services for the member or the eligibility of the member for products and services;To provide ongoing service;To detect and prevent fraud, and to help safeguard the financial interests of the credit union and its members;To meet legal and regulatory requirements; andTo meet personnel requirements.Consent: A member's knowledge and consent are required for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information, except in specific circumstances as described within this Code.Limiting Collection: We will limit the collection of personal information to that which is necessary for the purposes we identify. Information is always collected by fair and lawful means.Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention: We do not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which personal information was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required by law. We retain personal information only as long as necessary to meet the identified purposes or as required by law.Accuracy: We ensure that personal information is accurate, complete, and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes for which it is to be used. We rely on the member to keep certain personal information, such as address information, accurate, complete and up to date. We will update such information promptly when advised by the member or when the credit union otherwise learns of a change.Safeguards: Personal information is protected by security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. We apply the same standard of care as we apply to safeguard our own confidential information of a similar nature.Openness: We shall make readily available to members specific, understandable information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information within a reasonable length of time.Individual Access: Upon request or within a reasonable length of time, a member shall be informed of the existence, use, and disclosure of their personal information and shall be given access to that information. A member is entitled to question the accuracy and completeness of the information and have it amended as appropriate on proof of inaccuracy.Challenging Compliance: A member shall be able to question our compliance with the above principles to the Privacy Officer accountable for the credit union's compliance. A member is able to complete an Access Request, Inquiry or Complaint form to request access to personal information or to inquire or complain to the Privacy Officer.We welcome any questions or concerns about our Privacy Statement. Please contact us by e mail or in writing at the following address:Privacy OfficerMotor City Community Credit Unionprivacy@mcccu.com(519) 944-7455 extension 2376701 Tecumseh Road E., Windsor, N8T 1E8Notice:Motor City Community Credit Union reserves the right to amend its Privacy Statement at any time with or without notice.  Please check this page periodically for changes.
Online Privacy
This information page describes in general terms how your personal information is collected and used within the online banking section of our site. The online banking area of the site is the area of our website that requires you to use your Member ID and Password to enter.Controlled Access to your InformationTo ensure that you are the only person accessing your personal financial information, we restrict access to the online banking section of the site by requiring that you enter your Member ID and Password to login. Only you know your Password. Our employees do not have access to your Password, and they will not ask you to reveal it. If someone does ask you to provide your Password to them, we ask that you refuse to do so and contact us immediately.Transactional ServicesBy nature, our Internet banking site has many transactional functions such as transfers between accounts and bill payment functions. These transactions are all logged to ensure that your accounts are debited or credited appropriately, and a history of each transaction is available to verify your account information. We store and use your transactional information in the same fashion as if you performed the transaction at a branch or through any other service channel.We may also use transactional information for servicing your account — for example, billing you for the particular transactions that you perform, or for the services that you use.Creating a Secure ChannelWe create a secure channel between your browser and our server to protect your information when you use the site. To learn more about how we do this, please review our information on Internet Security.Application FormsTo provide you with a convenient method for applying for loans and mortgages, or for purchasing other financial services products such as Registered Savings Plans, we may provide secure online application forms. These forms capture personal information that we use to provide you with the products and services you request. This information is processed in a similar way to application forms received through our other channels .Website Usage StatisticsTo continually improve our site, we often collect statistics about how our members are using it. These usage statistics are only viewed in the aggregate and are not associated with you as an individual. We use this information for purposes such as improving the pages where our members are having difficulties.The information collected may include your IP address, your browser type and your operating system, as well as data such as the number and types of pages visited, and the length of time spent per page and on the site overall.Our use of CookiesWe also use a key web technology called cookies. A cookie is a small information token that sits on your computer. As you use this site, cookies are passed back and forth between our server and your browser.Specifically, we use two kinds of cookies — session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie exists only for the length of your browsing session and is deleted when you close your browser. A persistent cookie is a cookie that stays on your computer after you close your browser. A persistent cookie may or may not expire on a given date.We use a session cookie to maintain the integrity of your online banking session. With each page that you visit, the cookie is passed back and forth between our server and your browser. We use the cookie to distinguish your session from the many others that may be happening at the same time. Our session cookies never store any personal information, such as your name, or date of birth, or financial information, such as your accounts and balances.We may use persistent cookies to (i) provide you with a customized experience by recording your preferences; (ii) gather statistical information such as average time spent on a page; and (iii) to show you targeted marketing information about us when you visit other websites. The data gathered provides us with information on how we can improve the design, content and navigation of our website.Most recent browser versions allow you to set some level of control over which cookies are accepted and how your browser uses them. For example, it may be set to notify you when it is receiving a cookie so that you accept cookies from only known, reliable sites such as this one. If you are concerned about cookies, we encourage you to upgrade your browser to a recent version and review the Help section of your browser to learn more about its specific control features.Memorized Accounts FeatureWe use a persistent cookie to store information to help you personalize the site and to make it easier to use. For example, we allow you to make the login easier by remembering your login information within our Memorized Accounts feature. Since the Memorized Accounts feature is optional, this cookie only contains information that you have entered into it. We never store your Password in a cookie.Logout ButtonTo ensure that no-one else can access your personal information, always use the logout button to end an online banking session. It is located at the top of every page. When you exit using the logout button, we delete your session cookie so that your session cannot be resumed unless your Member ID and Password are re-entered.Automatic Session Time-outsIn the event that you leave your computer without logging out, the online banking feature of this site has been designed to end your session automatically if our system detects that you haven't provided any instructions or used the browser buttons to navigate for several minutes. To restart the session, you will need to provide your Password again.EmailTo communicate with us electronically, we strongly recommend that you use our Contact Us feature. This feature provides a secure channel for sending us comments, questions or instructions.General email is not secure since it passes through many points on its route from you to us. If you are using general email to communicate with us, we strongly recommend that you do not include personal financial information (such as account numbers) within the email as we cannot guarantee its confidentiality en route to us.When you email us your comments, questions or instructions, you provide us your email address and we use it to correspond with you. We then store your email and our replies to you in case we correspond further.Links to Other SitesOur site may also contain links to other websites or Internet resources. As an example, from time-to-time we may provide links to assist you in upgrading your Internet browser. However, we have no control over these other websites or Internet resources and do not control their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. Always review the Privacy Statements of the sites that you are viewing.Contact UsWe welcome any questions or concerns about your privacy relating to use of our website. Please use the Contact Us form to submit your questions or comments.As we continue to expand our online banking service to serve you better, and as new Internet technologies become available, we may update the information on this page at any time, to reflect changes.
BROWSE MOTOR CITY PRODUCTS
Accounts
Mortgages and Loans
Save and Invest
Credit Cards
CALL
519-944-7333
EMAIL
Chequing AccountsBusiness SolutionsYouth AccountCredit CardsMortgages and BorrowingSave and Invest
RatesMortgage and Loan CalculatorsService FeesWays to BankForeign Exchange
CONNECT
ContactSearchLocate Branch/ATM
FSRA
© 2020 Motor City Community Credit UnionLegal | Accessibility | Privacy & Security
© 2020 Motor City Community Credit UnionLegal | Accessibility | Privacy & Security
